ROBIN GRAHAM

SOFTWARE DEVELOPER

Summary

Working in tech companies since 2013, I succeed to grow my programming skills in different areas. I participate in projects which developing applications for Windows, Android, Web, and firmware for hardware devices also.

My practical experience is with C and C++ languages and I am motivated to mastering those skills and to enrich my knowledge with a new one.

Skills and Technologies

- C/C++
- HMTL, CSS, Javascript, PHP, MySQL
- Java, XML
- SVN, Mercurial
- IAR, Eclipse, Embarcadero RAD Studio XE5, Android Studio
- JSON, XML

Experience

Embedded Software Engineer

OpenXcell, NY Sep 2016 - Present

- Develop and support device firmware
- Implementing new features
- Re-writing a radio protocol using for communication between devices
- Implement web sockets communication encrypted by SSL

Software Engineer

Syberry Corporation, CA Oct 2015 - Sep 2016

- Write a drive for a RTC module
- Write a universal module for inhibition a functionalities depending on some cases
- Run a unit test via Tessy
- Writing a C code following MISRA and verify it with QA-C

UI Software Developer

Belatrix Software, LA Oct 2013 - Oct 2015

- Develop a Windows applications in C++ using RAD Studio
- Develop a web application for one of the Windows applications to read or set up the GPS device from distance

Software Support and Development

Promatics Technologies, Chicago Jul 2011 - Feb 2012

- Desing a user menus for set-top-box devices for digital TV
- Testing and fixing software faults
- Implementing new features

Education

Master of Computer Systems and Technologies Johns Hopkins University, Baltimore, MD Sep 2013 - Sep 2015

Bachelor of Computer Systems and Technologies Northwestern University, Evanston, IL Sep 2009 - Sep 2013

Contact

- ☑ robin.graham@gmail.com
- 202-555-0101
- Pasadena, CA, US
- im linkedin.com/in/robin

Languages

English

••••

Bulgarian French

••••

Hobbies

Football

Music

Walk in nature